Arrow, where are you taking me?
You want to skewer
this man's soul, too?
That boy will make
my sixth Stand user…
That should be more than enough.
I'll eliminate any wretch who dares
get close to my dear, Yoshikage!
TING
What?!
Ow.
W-What the blazes?
The arrow chose him,
but was deflected.
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
(Listen)
Breakdown, Breakdown
(3, 2, 1) Let's Go!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
Shining Justice begins to sprout
Brand-new bed town
Will we meet? Let's find out
Feeling the sea breeze from the cape
through the tunnel to the tower
We wander into the alley,
drawn to each other
A shadow melts into our hearts
But the golden spirits
shine a light to protect us
Let the voice of love
take you higher
Let the gathering forces
overcome time itself
1999 Bizarre Summer
Our courage keeps the town in bloom
Great Days
EPISODE 27
I'M AN ALIEN
Every piece of intel we could find
lies in that envelope.
PROFILE
YOSHIKAGE KIRA
He's done a fine job
of covering his tracks.
Yoshikage Kira…
Who's face are you hiding behind,
who's name have you stolen?
Where are you?
Summer…
Tourist season here in Morioh.
Yeah…
I doubt he'll be able to
stay quiet for long.
There's no way he can
resist his urges.
He'll be itching to act.
It's finally summer, everyone.
If you hadn't noticed,
July 1st marked the opening of
Morioh's beautiful rivers and be aches.
With masses of tourists descending
on our town from S City and beyond,
little ol' Morioh
is bound to be hopping.
Whether it's a little r and r,
camping, fishing, or yachting…
Morioh is your special summer paradise!
Now how are you going to
make the most of your summer?
A summer paradise, indeed…
Not just for them, but for him, too…
A summer paradise, indeed
We live our lives concealing
our deepest hopes and fears.
But…
To conceal forever, to everyone…
Can one live a lifetime
behind a veil of secrecy?
Damn it!
I want her to see
the true Yoshikage Kira.
To hear from my lips
the passion that burns within me…
To feel my hands wrapped
around her delicate neck,
as I wring the life from her heart.
As my nail growth surges,
so do my carnal desires.
I just need to persevere
until the urge subsides.
I still haven't mastered his signature.
KOSAKU KAWAJIRI
KOSAKU
Josuke Higashikata… Jotaro Kujo…
They're the reason
I'm in this predicament.
Um…
Uh… May I… ask what
you might be up to?
You're right.
I should just open my eyes.
You're reading a book.
Um, I made you some tea.
I know I don't usually
do this sort of thing,
b-but I thought maybe…
If you don't want any,
that's fine, too…
Oh, it's so late.
I suppose I should hit the sack…
Bare your heart to her.
Reveal to her your true self,
Yoshikage Kira.
Honey?
Shit. Baring my soul was a mistake.
They'll figure me out.
Sorry to have frightened you.
H-He was trying to unbutton my blouse?
"Sorry to have frightened you"?
Don't be sorry! This new you is…
is terribly exciting!
It's actually kind of turning me on! I…
I've fallen
in love with you.
J-Josuke, I-look over there.
What the heck is—
Is this… Could this be…
T-Terri Funk—
It's a crop circle!
Yeah! A crop circle!
Th-That's amazing!
To think one would pop up
in some field in Morioh!
Something's not right, Okuyasu.
Look closely, at the middle.
Shit, I can't believe this!
You're going in?
We don't have a choice!
Be careful.
Yeah.
I-Is he alive?
Well, he's got a little
scratch on the back of his neck,
but I think he only fainted.
Hey, wake up.
Are you all right? Hey!
I've never seen him
around at our school.
Oh, I think he's come to.
Where…
Where am I?
Where?
You're in the middle of
a field in Budogaoka, Morioh.
Is this Earth?
Yesterday evening,
I remember I suddenly felt unwell.
I must have then fell unconscious.
It is now past eight o'clock,
so I estimate I was unconscious
for nearly thirteen Earth hours.
You really had us going there!
Damn! That was one damn good prank!
Man, you got me good!
Dude, you are hilarious!
You made your own crop circle
and then waited
in a bunch of weeds
for someone to come by?
Amazing! Simply amazing!
I can't breathe! My stomach hurts!
STOMACH MEDICINE
It's freakin' ridiculous!
Which school do you go to?
- You're just our kind of guy!
- School?
My home planet once lay in
one of the Magellanic Clouds,
but has since been destroyed.
I've journeyed to earth to survey
the livability of its land
and the amiability of its people.
Quit while you're ahead.
That was an epic prank,
don't spoil it by trying too hard.
Here, have a tissue.
Thank you.
That was quite palatable.
Well, we really should be
getting to school.
Y-Yeah, you're right.
Let's go.
He decimated that tissue.
Someone thinks they're a comedian.
The ice cream store's closed!
It's the only thing that
makes Monday mornings bearable…
Nothing we can do about it.
Just forget about it.
Care for some ice cream?
Well? Would you like some?
Yeah, but the place's closed,
we're shit out of luck now.
That's no reason to give up.
I just so happen to have two here.
Consider it a quid pro quo
for the tissues.
Earth seems quite livable indeed.
It's cold…
W-Why do you have
ice cream cones in your bag?
Is the ice cream unsatisfactory?
That's not the point!
Who the hell are you?
I believe I already told you…
Ah! You want me
to introduce myself.
How could I forget…
My name is Nu Mikitakazo Nushi.
I am 216 years old.
I am a spaceship pilot.
I like having pets.
I'm currently carrying
a house mouse in my bag.
He adores it when I brush his back.
This freak's a Stand user.
No doubt about it.
Let's show him
what a hospital looks like!
Hold your horses, Okuyasu.
Do you really think a Stand user
would say that he's from
the Magellanic Clouds?
- Then what the hell is he?
- There, there, there.
I don't have the foggiest idea.
Time to conduct our own survey.
Don't eat that ice cream.
Huh?!
So you're 216, huh?
Yes.
- Hmm…
So you're a spaceship pilot?
Why do you keep mimicking me?
So, what?
You trying to say you're an alien?
An alien!
An alien! Yes!
I suppose I should have
mentioned that initially.
I am an alien.
Hey, hey, hey, hey…
So, then, you have a…
flying saucer?
Could you call over your spaceship?
You can, right?
Of course.
Unfortunately,
it is currently standing by
at an altitude of
1,500,000 kilometers,
so it would take
approximately three days.
Anything else is futile.
Do you call it with that watch?
Oh, how did you know?
But this must stay
between the three of us.
You must not share this
with anyone.
This guy's more than a little cuckoo.
That wasn't some innocent little prank.
He's a delusional psychopath.
Maybe I should knock
that nose ring to the floor?
You always let your fists
do the talking.
Just to be sure,
let's dig a little deeper.
Do you have some kinda ray gun or
or ultra hyper anti-gravity device
in there?
Of course I do.
But I did not journey here
to engage in conflict,
so I left them in my spaceship.
Aw, come on.
You're an alien,
show us something cool.
And your blood wasn't even green.
Yeah. Alien blood is always green.
Do you doubt
my extraterrestrialness?
Hey, calm down.
You finally figured it out,
huh, dumb-ass!
I can deal with a little prank
here and there,
but I refuse to shoot the breeze
with a lunatic like you.
I cannot believe
you just said that!
Shut up! It's always better
to say it like it is!
What? Did a fire
break out somewhere?
W-What the hell?
This sound…
I can't stand this sound.
Stop this sound!
I can't stand this sound!
I'm allergic to this sound!
Make it stop!
Josuke, this guy's dangerous!
Let's go. We should
stay far away from him.
Yeah, but…
We can't just
abandon him like that.
He said it was just allergies.
Leave him be.
I'm outta here, Josuke.
H-Hey!
Damn it, Okuyasu.
H-Hey, you okay?
Please, take me away…
take me away from this sound…
W-What?!
Take me away from this sound!
So then you're a…
I have the power to
transform into anything.
H-Hurry… This sound
is going to split my head in two…
I beg you…
I'll turn into sneakers, so please,
put them on and get me out of here!
In return,
I'll do anything you ask!
Are you a Stand user?!
Whoa! Y-Your speed is amazing!
With your power and
my power combined,
our speed and jumping ability
are doubled.
Are you really an alien?!
TERRA VENTUS
What the hell is going on?!
You…
You can't see this?
He can't see it!
He's not a Stand user.
Then what the hell is this power?
What the hell are you?!
You are stubborn, aren't you?
I have been telling you
I am an alien…
Just give me a second.
I've gotta wrap my head
around this.
Anyhow, I appreciate
your saving me from that situation.
The people on my planet
truly abhor the sound of sirens.
It is a very upsetting
wavelength for us.
I would like to repay your kindness
for rescuing me.
Shall I turn into a fan
to refresh you?
Or perhaps a back scratcher
to scratch your back?
Whoa, I didn't save you cause
I wanted a favor from you…
You'll really do anything?
Okay! Then do it! Pretty please!
SHOPPING
CATALOG
What is it that you request of me?
C-Can you turn into anything?
Like something light,
or multiples of something?
Yes. I can transform
into nearly anything.
However,
becoming complex machinery
or anything more powerful than me
is unfeasible.
I see, I see. Got it. I like you!
So you want to thank me, right?
Yes.
You know I just…
thought of a great idea.
It's gonna be a win-win
for all parties involved.
Win-win?
Yeah!
See, I won a little spending money
recently in the local lottery,
then my mom found out
and froze my account.
Once that woman makes up her mind,
your fate is sealed.
Being flat broke for the summer
is the worst.
SHOPPING
CATALOG
That's why…
Can you turn into this? Right here.
What is that?
They're called dice!
I'll make some cash with these,
then split the winnings with you,
thus creating a win-win situation!
What do they do?
Huh? You don't know what dice are?
My apologies…
It's nothing to be sorry for.
It's super easy. I'll show you.
Anyone who likes playing games
goes nuts over these things.
They've got six sides
and are made from hard material.
This dot represents the number one,
and each face has
a different number, up to six.
Ah, yes.
It's starting to make sense.
So five dots means
the number five, right?
Impressive, Mr. alien!
- And three dots represent a three.
- Yes! Try turning into one.
At your service, Sir.
It is simple.
I think you're a little confused.
You went a little too big.
I'm thinkin' this big.
Also, you've got five on two sides.
Each face has a different
number of dots from one to six.
The numbers on one side and its
opposite side should equal seven.
Oh, my apologies.
How's this?
Th-That tickles!
Hey, don't laugh.
Dice aren't supposed to talk.
Huh?
Come on.
I-I'll try harder.
I'm a bit nervous about this, but…
Yes, you're good! Very good!
This is perfect!
Now I'm getting excited!
Rohan Kishibe,
- you better have some cashola ready!
- I-I can't breathe…
Oh, well what a surprise.
Now why would Josuke Higashikata
be visiting me?
This is certainly
out of the ordinary.
Did you uncover more dirt on Kira?
No, not exactly…
Um, well…
So, finished with work for the day?
I was wondering if you'd let me
take a peek at the next volume…
Just what are you scheming now?
Come on, spit it out.
Well, whaddya know…
I can't hide anything from you,
Rohan-sensei.
All right, I confess.
Here's the deal.
I'm begging you!
Please play Cee-Io with me!
Cee-Io?
Okay, let me be perfectly honest…
It's summer,
and I'm totally strapped for cash.
Well, I do have 30,000 yen.
That's all I got to my name.
But…
Nowadays, 30,000 yen won't get you
more than a couple of visits to
the amusement park and some food.
So I either make me some dough,
or go flat broke.
Take a risk and enjoy the thrill!
Isn't that what being young
is all about?
I think so at least! Don't you?!
Look, let me be frank.
I've never liked you.
So why in god's name
should I play Cee-Io with you?
I guess you're right.
You're not exactly
hurting for cash,
- there's no reason for you to play.
- But… All right.
Huh?! You'll do it?
I don't dislike games,
besides, I'm fascinated.
Come around to the back.
Thank you, Rohan-sensei.
THE SHOOTER ROLLS 3 DICE
INTO THE BOWL
THIS WILL RESULT IN WINNING DOUBLE
THE LARGER NUMBER WINS
(HERE, THE 6)
THIS WILL RESULT IN PAYING DOUBLE
Do these rules work for you?
Looks good to me.
Each chip is worth 1,000 yen.
Try to roll the three dice
into the bowl,
if even one falls out, you lose.
Got it.
All right. The rules can go here.
- Okay, let's get this game started!
- Wait.
We won't be using that dice.
Huh?!
We'll be using these dice
I had in the house.
U-Um, is there something
you don't like about my dice?
Not really. I feel inclined
to use mine instead, that's all.
And…
When I mentioned I was fascinated,
it wasn't by Cee-Io.
I was fascinated by
the prospect of swiping 30,000 yen
from your almost yenless hands.
When you lose,
I expect you to pay in full.
I don't care how much we've
been through together, Josuke.
Yes! Those dice are actually the alien!
I snuck them into his house
when he wasn't looking!
Oh, I am so bad
It won't be a ton,
but you're about to fund
my summer vacay, Rohan-sensei
Now, shall we determine
who gets to go first.
A four.
Yes!
Well, looks like you're first.
Roll.
Ow!
O…
O-Ow! I just banged my hand
into the table.
Just place your bet
and role the dice.
R-Right…
I-I think I'll start off with two,
so then, 2,000 yen.
Got it, here's two chips.
If I roll a one, a two,
and a three,
I'll have to pay double,
so I just have to avoid
one, two, and three at all costs.
Just stay away from
one, two, and three!
I can't get one, two, and three!
The first roll calls for
a light touch I think.
Always gotta warm up…
Here we go… Nice and gentle.
How's that?!
- Huh?!
- What?
It's an omen…
What?
Triple sixes, AKA "omen."
Josuke wins five times
what he wagered from Rohan.
You dumb ass! You can't just
start with that kind of hand!
E-Er, I mean…
I mean talk about dumb luck!
A triple six and five times
the winnings…
It almost looks like I'm cheating!
Hmph. So you've already
earned 10,000 yen in change.
- I'm in disbelief myself…
- Let's continue.
I guess I'm next then.
I want to recover
what I just lost, so I'm…
going with ten.
Ten?
All right! There!
One, two, and three.
The wager is doubled!
THIS WILL RESULT IN PAYING DOUBLE
THE SHOOTER ROLLS 3 DICE
INTO THE BOWL
Rohan must pay double his wager.
He's taking it too far!
It's getting obvious!
Does this alien have
any concept of holding back?
Shit… He's gotta think
things are fishy now!
EPISODE 28
HIGHWAY GO GO, PART 1